Guide to the Robert F. Curl Academic papers, 1953- 2012, bulk 1985-1993 MS 483
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XII: Correspondence, 2005-2008
  - Research Publications, 1955-2011
    - Infrared Matrix Isolation Studies of Nuclear-Spin-Species Conversion, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Microwave Spectrum of Acryloyl Fluoride, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Theoretical Calculations of the Kinetics of the Order-Disorder Transition in CO..., 1968 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Simple Stark Modulation Absorption System for High Temperature Microwave, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Microwave Spectrum, Conformation and Dipole Movement of Divinyl Ether, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Table of Observed Lines of Chlorine Dioxide (typescript), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Fluorescence Spectrum of Chlorine Dioxide, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Observation of a Pure Rotational Q-Branch Transition of Methane, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Computer Controlled IR Spectrometer Using a Color Center Laser, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Color-Center Laser Spectroscopy of Small Free Radicals, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Computer Control of Broadly Tunable Lasers, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Experimental Observations Regarding Transition States, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Magnetic Rotation Spectroscopy of C2H Free Radical with Color Center Laser, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Tunable Infrared Color Center Lasers, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Color-Center Laser Spectroscopy of Transient Species..., 1985 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Observation of the v1 Rotation-Vibration Band of the NCO Radical, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Photoexcitation of Reaction Complexes in...K+NaCl+KCl+Na, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Multiwavenumber Linearized Diode Laser Spectra, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Rate Constant Measurements of Reactions of C2H with H2, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Photophysics of Metal Complexes of Spheroidal Carbon Shells, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Biography of Kenneth S. Pitzer, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Efficient Production of C80 (Buckminster Fullerene), C60H36, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - CW Difference Frequency Generation in AgGaS2, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Measurement of Nonlinear Coefficient and Phase Matching Characteristics of AgGaS2, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Pre-1990 Evidence for the Fullerene Proposal, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Continuous-Wave Tunable 8.7-um Spectroscopic Source, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Continuously tunable long-wavelength cw IR Source for High-Resolution Spectroscopy, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Dawn of the Fullerenes: Experiment and Conjecture Nobel Lecture, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Room Temperature Mid-Infrared Laser Sensor for Trace Gas Detection, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Detection of Formaldehyde using Mid-Infrared Difference-Frequency Generation, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - C-D Stretch of Monodeuterated Propargyl Radical (CH2CCD), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Analysis of the K-Subband Structure of the V1 Fundamental of Propargyl Radical, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Fibre Coupled Difference Frequency Generation Utilizing Ytterbium-Doped, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Mid-Infrared Difference-Frequency Generation Source Pumped by a 1.1-1.5-um, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Compact Mid-Infrared Trace Gas Sensor Based on Difference-Frequency Generation, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Rotationally Resolved Infrared Spectrum of the v1 Stretch of the Allyl Radical, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Real-Time Measurements of Trace Gases Using a Compact Difference-Frequency-Based, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - v1 and v1+v5 of DCCN: Determination of the V5 energy and the quasilinearity of DCCN, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Tunable Infrared Laser Sources: From the Laboratory Towards the Rice Paddy, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Rotational Analysis of V13 of Allyl Radical, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - High-Power Continuous-Wave Mid-Infrared Radiation Generated by Difference, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - V1+V5 Band of HCCN: Determination of the V5 Vibrational Energy, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Methane Concentration and Isotopic Composition Measurements, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Kinetics of the Reaction of Propargyl Radical with Nitric Oxide, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Effective Utilization of Quantum-Cascade Distributed-Feedback Lasers, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Far-Infrared LMR Spectroscopic Investigation of the Quasi-linear Molecule DCCN, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Photolysis of NO2 at 193 nm, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Spectroscopic Detection of Biological NO with a Quantum Cascade Laser, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Reactions of NH2 with NO2 and of OH with NH2O, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - High-Resolution Infrared Spectroscopic Determination of the..., 2001 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Field Measurements of Volcanic Gases Using Tunable Diode Laser Based Mid-Infrared..., 2002 (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Transportable Automated Ammonia Sensor Based on a Pulsed Themoelectrically..., 2002 (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - High-Resolution Infrared Spectra of Jet-Cooled Allyl Radical (CH2-CH-CH2), 2002 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Tunable Infrared Laser Spectroscopy, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - High-Resolution Infrared Spectra of the C-H Asymmetric Stretch Vibration..., 2002 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Chemical Sensing with Pulsed QC-DFB Lasers Operating at 15.6 um, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Quartz-Enhanced Photoacoustic Spectroscopy, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - High-Resolution Jet-Cooled and Room Temperature Infrared Spectra of the v3 CH Stretch, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - Kinetic Study of the Reaction of Acetaldehyde with OH, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - Mid-Infrared Quantum Cascade Laser-Based Off-Axis..., 2004 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - Atmospheric Formaldehyde Monitoring Houston..., 2002 (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Monitoring of Ethylene by a Pulsed Quantum Cascade Laser, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Pulsed Quantum-Cascade Laser-Based Sensor for Trace-Gas..., 2004 (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Formaldehyde Sensor Using Interband Cascade Laser-Based Quartz-Enhanced..., 2004 (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - IR Kinetic Spectroscopy Investigation of the CH4 + O(1D) Reaction, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 83)
    - Color-blind Fluorescence Detection for Four-Color DNA Sequencing, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 84)
    - Widely Tunable Mode-hop Free External Cavity Quantum Cascade Laser..., 2005 (Box 21, Folder 85)
    - Sub-ppbv Nitric Oxide Concentration Measurements Using CW Thermoelectrically, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 86)
    - Observation of Hot Bands in the Infrared Spectrum of H2CO, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 87)
    - Development of the Hamiltonian and Matrix Elements for Partially Deuterated..., 2007 (Box 21, Folder 88)
    - Jet-Cooled Spectrum of Methoxy in the CH Stretching Region, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - Application of Quantum Cascade Lasers to Trace Gas Analysis, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - Widely Tunable Mode-hop Free External Cavity Quantum Cascade Lasers, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Wide-Field Four0Channel Fluorescence Imager for Biological Applications, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Economics of Pricing the cost of Carbon Dioxide Restrictions in Electricity, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Spectroscopic Characterization of the Methoxy Radical III Rotationally Resolved..., 2011 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Research Files
    - Notes, Calculations, Correspondence, 1970-1990 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Notes on CAMAC (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - Supersonic Jet Plans (Box 21, Folder 97)
    - White Cell Oven (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - Laseer Mirrors (Box 21, Folder 99)
    - CICN, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 100)
    - Mütek, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 101)
    - Coherent Interrupt (Box 21, Folder 102)
    - CS2, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 103)
    - Parity of Doublet PI Molecules (Box 21, Folder 104)
    - Check of Our Program for C2H (Box 21, Folder 105)
    - Sean O'Brien's C4 Data (Box 21, Folder 106)
    - W2 of Ketene (Box 21, Folder 107)
    - Inorganic Forces (Box 21, Folder 108)
    - Noise and Signal in Jet Absorption (Box 21, Folder 109)
    - C2H+H2 Kinetics (Box 21, Folder 110)
    - Gaussian Beams (Box 21, Folder 111)
    - Sears HCO (Box 21, Folder 112)
    - C2H 2928 Band (Box 21, Folder 113)
    - Curve of Growth, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 114)
    - Kanamori's Data, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 115)
    - EPA Auto Emissions, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 116)
    - Thermal Conductivity, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 117)
    - LMR by Laser Pulling (Box 21, Folder 118)
    - HE Sat Spectroscopy (Box 21, Folder 119)
    - CO CCL DR Signal (Box 21, Folder 120)
    - Cooling of a Soot Particle (Box 21, Folder 121)
    - Fast IR KS (Box 21, Folder 122)
    - Thermal Motion of Targets: Zake, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 123)
    - Diagnostic Least: Squares Fitting (Box 21, Folder 124)
    - Gas Kinetic Theory (Box 21, Folder 125)
    - Matrix Isolation (Box 21, Folder 126)
    - Optics Talks (Box 21, Folder 127)
    - Rotation-Vibration Interaction (Box 21, Folder 128)
    - JWS Notes on Least Squares Program (Box 21, Folder 129)
    - C2H2, Kermit Murray, ACS, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 130)
    - Global Monitoring, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 131)
    - Remote Sensing, 1983-1995 (Box 21, Folder 132)
    - AgGaS2 Properties, 1971-1987 (Box 21, Folder 133)
    - Misc. Papers on Non-Linear, 1971-1989 (Box 21, Folder 134)
    - Phase Matching Calculations, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Coherent Laser Group, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - EXP Results, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Cleveland Crystals, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - AgGaS2 Data, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - C2H Perturbations, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Kinetic Spectroscopy (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - HNF, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - 3500 Spectrum (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - CO Infrared Bands (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - CCH Analysis, H. Kanamori, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Marilyn Jacox, National Bureau of Standards, 1986, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Marilyn Jacox's Spectra, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Marilyn Jacox and W. Bruse Olson, A2-X2E+ Transition of HC2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Infrared Detectors (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - CCLS Sensitivity, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - FCL Alignment (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Burleigh FCL Records, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - IODR, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - White Cell Plans, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Bonn Design Small White Cell, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Karl Smolka White Cell, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - DFL White Cell/Boxless (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - References, Misc., 1960s-1970s (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - CsAr, 1974-1978 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - CS-M Theory, S. Mukamel (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Chip's Mathcad Caluclations, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - M.M. Fejer, Nonlinear Frequency Conversion, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Prie, Byer and Herbert and Others, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Tran-ba Chu Papers, 1977-1985 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Thermal Lensing Conduction and Absorption (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Ohio State DFG Figures (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - DFG IRKS Illustrative Figures (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Alan Button (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Chromatrix Oven Controller, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Autocam Software, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - S1O2 Overcoated Mirrors, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - ZnGeP2 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Bayard and Hilcher, Computer Control of 699-21 Laser, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Bhax et al., Tunable Parametric ZnGeP2 Crystal Oscillator, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Vodopyanov et al., High Efficiency Middle IR Parametric Superradince in..., 1991 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Important Numbers for "Back of the Envelope" Calculations (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Collision Times (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Absorption Lineshapes (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Diagnostic Least Squares Fitting of Spectroscopic Data (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Cincinnati Electronics (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Noyes and Furrow, The Oscillatory Briggs-Rauscher Reaction 3, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Wall, Alternative Derivations of the Statistical Mechanical Distribution Laws, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Laser Noise, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Lyman-Ox Absorption, 1966-1985 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Michelson Wavemeter Manual, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - OH Stretch of Hydroxy Methyl (CH2OH), 1978-1991 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Fullerene Isomer Effect, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - C60 Symmetry (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Efforts to Improve Reaction Complex, 1969-1989 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Spectroscopy of Jet-Cooled Transient Systems, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Nuclear Spin Isomerization, 1967-1990 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Transient Digitizers, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Absorption Cross-Section for the OH Fundamental (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Absorption Cross-Section for the OH Fundamental (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Cs Atom-Sharma Data (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - C2 Lineshapes Checks (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - C2 Lineshapes, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lineshapes Decomposition (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Lineshapes, Before 1982-05-23 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Lineshapes, 1982-05-23-1982-05-30 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Lineshape Drawings, 1982-05-31-1982-06-01 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - G Factor and MR Signal, Old, 1982-06-03 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - New Sign G12, 1982-06-06 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Lineshape Calculations, 1982-07-08-1982-07-10 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Lineshapes, 1982-07-10-1982-07-11 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Jeff Cook's Radical Program, 1987-07 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Tone Modulation, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Cd Te Modulator, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Namba, Electro-Optical Effect of Zincblende, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Computer (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Beaudet Program (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - 1170 Programs: FCL Analysis Pro, HP (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Course Material, 1960-2005
    - CHEM 230, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - CHEM 310a, 310b: Physical Chemistry (1 of 5), 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - CHEM 310a, 310b: Physical Chemistry (2 of 5), 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - CHEM 310a, 310b: Physical Chemistry (3 of 5), 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - CHEM 310a, 310b: Physical Chemistry (4 of 5), 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - CHEM 310a, 310b: Physical Chemistry (5 of 5), 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, Curl's Master Copy (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, Curl's Master Copy (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, Course Outline, Undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, problems, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab 1st Exam, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab 2nd Exam, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab 3rd Exams, 1981-1985 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, 1981-1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Course Schedule, Reading and Homework Assignments (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Course Schedule, Reading and Homework Assignments (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Course Schedule, Reading and Homework Assignments (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, Lectures, Handouts, Homework Assignments (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Lectures, Handouts, Homework Assignments (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Lectures, Handouts, Homework Assignments (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab, Assignments, Course Outline, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Homework, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Schedule, Lectures, Homework (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Schedule, Lectures, Homework (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Class Notes, Exams, Problems (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Class Notes, Exams, Problems (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Class Notes, Exams, Problems (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - CHEM 311a: Physical Chemistry Lab: Homework and Exams, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - CHEM 312: Physical Chemistry: Homework, Exams, Handouts, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - CHEM 415/515: Chemical Kinetics: Schedule, Handouts, Homework, Exams (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - CHEM 415/515: Chemical Kinetics: Schedule, Handouts, Homework, Exams (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - CHEM 430: Quantum Chemistry, Schedule, Exams, Homework, Handouts, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - CHEM 430: Quantum Chemistry, Schedule, Exams Homework, Handouts (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - CHEM 430: Quantum Chemistry, Schedule, Exams, Homework, Handouts (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - CHEM 430/530: Quantum Chemistry: Lecture Notes, Problems, Exams, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - CHEM 450: Thermodynamics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (1 of 3), 1960-1968 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - CHEM 450: Thermodynamics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (2 of 3), 1960-1968 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - CHEM 450: Thermodynamics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (3 of 3), 1960-1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - CHEM 471b: Molecular Spectroscopy: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (1 of 4), 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - CHEM 471b: Molecular Spectroscopy: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (2 of 4), 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - CHEM 471b: Molecular Spectroscopy: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (3 of 4), 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - CHEM 471b: Molecular Spectroscopy: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (4 of 4), 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - CHEM 521a: Chemical Thermodynamics: Lecture notes, homework, exams (1 of 3), 1979, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - CHEM 521a: Chemical Thermodynamics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (2 of 3), 1979, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - CHEM 521a: Chemical Thermodynamics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (3 of 3), 1979, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - CHEM 630: Molecular Spectroscopy: Schedule, Handouts, Homework (1 of 3), 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - CHEM 630: Molecular Spectroscopy: Schedule, Handouts, Homework (2 of 3), 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - CHEM 630: Molecular Spectroscopy Schedule, Handouts, Homework (3 of 3), 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (1 of 9), 1962-1975, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (2 of 9), 1962-1975 and undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (3 of 9), 1962-1975, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (4 of 9), 1962-1975, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (5 of 9), 1962-1975, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (6 of 9), 1962-1975, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (7 of 9), 1962-1975, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (8 of 9), 1962-1975, Undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - CHEM 650: Quantum Mechanics: Lecture Notes, Homework, Handouts, Exams (9 of 9), 1962-1975, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - CHEM 651a: Quantum Mechanics, Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - CHEM 651a: Quantum Mechanics, Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - CHEM 652b: Quantum Mechanics, Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - CHEM 652b: Quantum Mechanics Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - CHEM 652b: Quantum Mechanics Lecture Notes, Homework, Exams (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - UNIV 113: Technological Disasters and Catastrophes, Course Outline, Student Packet (1 of 3), 1999, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - UNIV 113: Technological Disasters and Catastrophes, Course Outline, Student Packet (2 of 3), 1999, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - UNIV 113: Technological Disasters and Catastrophes, Course Outline, Student Packet (3 of 3), 1999, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Electronic Media
    - Alfred Nobel: The Man and the Prize (Box 28, Item 1)
    - Falun Gong (Falun Dafa) Introduction (Box 28, Item 2)
    - Curl, "Technological Disasters and Our Evolving World" St. Mary's University, 2002-10-03 (Box 28, Item 3)
    - Nova C60 (Box 28, Item 4)
    - Smalley, R.E. Rehearsal Presentation: Nanotechnology, 1995-05-02 (Box 28, Item 5)
    - Nobel Prize: CNN-TV, 1996-12-08 (Box 28, Item 6)
    - Nobel Prize: Nobel Ceremony, 1996 (Box 28, Item 7)
    - Nobel Prize: Chemistry Nobel Award (3 copies), 1996 (Box 28, Item 8-10)
    - Nobel Prize: Nobel International Highlights Program, 1996 (Box 28, Item 11)
    - Nobel Prize: Nobel Highlights, 1996 (Box 28, Item 12)
    - Lindau: Meeting of Nobel Laureates (2 Copies), 2006 (Box 28, Item 13-14)
    - Science and Innovation Week: Mexico City (2 Copies), 2011-10 (Box 28, Item 15-16)
    - Klaus Smolka Correspondence (Box 28, Item 17)
    - Final Nozzle Plans (Box 28, Item 18)
    - Box Plans and Flanges (2 Copies) (Box 28, Item 19)
  - Memorabilia (Oversize)
    - Rice University: Harry Carothers and Olga Keith Wiess Chair in Natural Sciences, 1989 (Box 29, Item 1)
    - Rice University: Kenneth S. Pitzer: Schlumberger Chair, 2002 (Box 29, Item 2)
    - U.S. Patent Office no. 2,101,057 to Buckminster Fuller, 1933-10-18 (Box 29, Item 3)
    - U.S. Patent Office no. 4,377,114 to Buckminster Fuller (Box 29, Item 4)
    - Photographs: Texas Heart Institute, 2008-12-04 (Box 29, Item 5)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1996-10-10 (Box 29, Item 6)
    - Dallas Morning News (2 Copies) (Box 29, Item 7)
    - USA Today, 1996-10-10 (Box 29, Item 8)
    - Houston Chronicle, 1996-10-10 (Box 29, Item 9)
    - Institution of Mechanical Engineers (U.K.): James Clayton Fund Prize, 1957 (Box 29, Item 10)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Membership, 1998 (Box 29, Item 11)
    - American Physical Society International Prize for New Materials, 1992 (Box 29, Item 12)
    - Manufacturing Hall of Fame, 2012 (Box 29, Item 13)
    - Current Trends in Computational Chemisty, 2012 (Box 29, Item 14)
    - Russia: Tesla Global Forum, 2013 (Box 29, Item 15)
    - MeHarry Medical College Distinguished Scholar Award, 2001 (Box 29, Item 16)
    - Japanese Recognition Scroll (Box 30)
    - India: B.M. Birla Science Center, Hyderabad Life Achievement in Science, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Certificates
    - Kentucky Colonel, 2013 (Box 32, Item 1)
    - State of Texas Resolution, 2008 (Box 32, Item 2)
    - NASA Space Act Award, 1998 (Box 32, Item 3)
    - NASA Certificate of Recognition, 1998 (Box 32, Item 4)
    - NASA Certificate of Recognition, 2008 (Box 32, Item 5)
    - NASA Tech Brief Initial Award, 2010 (Box 32, Item 6)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 2010 (Box 32, Item 7)
    - Nobel Prize Laureates Meeting Memorable Medal, 2008 (Box 32, Item 8)
    - Germany: Humboldt Award, 1983 (Box 32, Item 9)
    - France: Clubs UNESCO, Cross-Cultural Ambassador, 2013 (Box 32, Item 10)
    - Isreal: Bar-Ilan University Honorary Doctorate, 2010 (Box 32, Item 11)